[{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"on the y-axis.","answerB":"in the first quadrant.","answerC":"in the four quadrant.","answerD":"on the x-axis.","id":1,"question":"The ordered pair (3,0) is found: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"N is a function, f, of t.","answerB":"f is a function, N, of t.","answerC":"N is a function, t, of f.","answerD":"t is a function, f, of N.","id":2,"question":"Which of the following is the correct description of N=f(t)?","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":2,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"calculus quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"B","answerA":"I quadrant","answerB":"II quadrant","answerC":"III quadrant","answerD":"IV quadrant","id":3,"question":"(-3, 7) is located in quadrant: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"on the y-axis.","answerB":"in the first quadrant.","answerC":"in the four quadrant.","answerD":"on the x-axis.","id":4,"question":"The ordered pair (3,0) is found: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"on the y-axis.","answerB":"in the first quadrant.","answerC":"in the four quadrant.","answerD":"on the x-axis.","id":5,"question":"The ordered pair (3,0) is found: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"on the y-axis.","answerB":"in the first quadrant.","answerC":"in the four quadrant.","answerD":"on the x-axis.","id":6,"question":"The ordered pair (3,0) is found: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"N is a function, f, of t.","answerB":"f is a function, N, of t.","answerC":"N is a function, t, of f.","answerD":"t is a function, f, of N.","id":7,"question":"Which of the following is the correct description of N=f(t)?","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":2,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"calculus quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"on the y-axis.","answerB":"in the first quadrant.","answerC":"in the four quadrant.","answerD":"on the x-axis.","id":8,"question":"The ordered pair (3,0) is found: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"N is a function, f, of t.","answerB":"f is a function, N, of t.","answerC":"N is a function, t, of f.","answerD":"t is a function, f, of N.","id":9,"question":"Which of the following is the correct description of N=f(t)?","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":2,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"calculus quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"on the y-axis.","answerB":"in the first quadrant.","answerC":"in the four quadrant.","answerD":"on the x-axis.","id":10,"question":"The ordered pair (3,0) is found: ","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":1,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"algebra quiz"}},{"actAnswer":"A","answerA":"N is a function, f, of t.","answerB":"f is a function, N, of t.","answerC":"N is a function, t, of f.","answerD":"t is a function, f, of N.","id":11,"question":"Which of the following is the correct description of N=f(t)?","quizzesId":{"creatorId":{"email":"lecturer@gmail.com","fname":"Jane","id":2,"lname":"Doe","password":"lecturerpassword","updateTime":"2015-04-19T05:01:36+01:00","username":"lecturer1","userrole":"LECTURER"},"id":2,"subjectId":{"id":1,"title":"maths"},"title":"calculus quiz"}}]